macsurfer.com 2006-10-16

# MacSurfer's Privacy Policy

MacSurfer's Headline News has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for our website.

**IP Address & Cookies**  
We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our servers, as part of our internal log processing, and to otherwise administer our Web site. We may use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our sites. 

**Registration Information**  
Our site's registration forms may require users to give us contact information (like their name and email address). The customer's contact information is used solely by MacSurfer's Headline News to contact the visitor when necessary. For example, we direct e-mail to visitors who provide us with their e-mail addresses for specifically requested purposes such as receiving our e-mail newsletters or being notified if they have won one of our contests. Each e-mail newsletter always contains instructions on how to unsubscribe from the newsletter. We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer outside the company personally identifiable information that visitors voluntarily provide in any registration or contest submission unless specifically noted during the submission process. This information is used to better understand visitors' use of our sites and to support related transactions made on the site. 

**Third party links**  
In an attempt to provide increased value to our visitors, our sites provide links to various third party web sites from our own site. However, even if the third party is affiliated with MacSurfer's Headline News, MacSurfer's Headline News has no control over these linked sites who each have separate privacy and data collection practices, independent of MacSurfer's Headline News. MacSurfer's Headline News has no responsibility or liability for these independent policies or actions and is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites. These linked sites are only for your convenience and you therefore access them at your own risk. Nonetheless, MacSurfer's Headline News seeks to protect the integrity of its web site and the links placed upon it and therefore requests any feedback on not only its own site, but for sites it links to as well (including if a specific link does not work). 

**Online Surveys**  
Our online surveys ask visitors for contact information (including, but not limited to, their email address) and demographic information (including, but not limited to, their zip code, age, or income level). The customer's contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may cancel future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. 

**Site Advertisers**  
We use outside ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received from banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not necessarily have access to this information. 

**Public Forums**  
This site may, at some time, make chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

**Security**  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. 

**Choice/Opt-Out**  
Our sites provide users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us during the registration process. Our sites give users the option to remove their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. 

**Contacting MacSurfer's Headline News**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: 

Publisher & Editor-in-Chief: P. Pearson [ppearson@technn.com](mailto:ppearson@technn.com)
